This website uses cookie files for the purpose of analyzing user activity levels, showing relevant ads and improving your experience. You can refuse to use cookies by declining; however this might affect how some site features work. By using this site, you agree to allow our third-party partners to utilize this technology in the manner and for the purposes described above.

Accept Decline [Privacy Policy](https://jefawk.com/privacy-policy.html)

[Spaghettorium](https://jefawk.com/index.html)Toggle navigation

Terms and Conditions
====================

Welcome to JeFawk's Spaghettorium! 👋🍻

Our Products
------------

The term "our products" refers to everything we create and make available to the public, whether free or paid. This includes our games, apps, programs, books, art, writing (such as blog posts, short stories, books, novels, and compilations), and both digital and physical products (like stickers, prints, books, bookmarks, magnets, etc.).

y using this website and purchasing or using our products, you agree to adhere to our Terms and Conditions and acknowledge the associated [Disclaimers](https://jefawk.com/legal/disclaimers.html). If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use our website or products.

Accessing our website and ordering our products implies acceptance of these Terms and Conditions.

* * *

These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of our games, programs, digital and physical products, located at https://jefawk.com and its subdomains.

The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: "Client", "You" and "Your" refers to you, the person log on this website and compliant to the Company’s terms and conditions. "The Company", "Ourselves", "We", "Our" and "Us", refers to our Company. "Party", "Parties", or "Us", refers to both the Client and ourselves. All terms refer to the offer, acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner for the express purpose of meeting the Client’s needs in respect of provision of the Company’s stated services, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing law of Netherlands. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalization and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.

### **Cookies**

We employ the use of cookies. By accessing JeFawk.com, you agreed to use cookies in agreement with the JeFawk Games's Privacy Policy.

Most interactive websites use cookies to let us retrieve the user’s details for each visit. Cookies are used by our website to enable the functionality of certain areas to make it easier for people visiting our website. Some of our affiliate/advertising partners may also use cookies.

### **License**

Unless otherwise stated, JeFawk Games and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on JeFawk.com. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this from JeFawk.com for your own personal use subjected to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.

Unless you have our written agreement, you must not:

* Republish material from JeFawk.com
* Sell, rent or sub-license material from JeFawk.com
* Reproduce, duplicate or copy material from JeFawk.com
* Redistribute content from JeFawk.com

This Agreement shall begin on the date hereof.

Parts of this website offer an opportunity for users to post and exchange opinions and information in certain areas of the website. JeFawk Games does not filter, edit, publish or review Comments prior to their presence on the website. Comments do not reflect the views and opinions of JeFawk Games,its agents and/or affiliates. Comments reflect the views and opinions of the person who post their views and opinions. To the extent permitted by applicable laws, JeFawk Games shall not be liable for the Comments or for any liability, damages or expenses caused and/or suffered as a result of any use of and/or posting of and/or appearance of the Comments on this website.

JeFawk Games reserves the right to monitor all Comments and to remove any Comments which can be considered inappropriate, offensive or causes breach of these Terms and Conditions.

You warrant and represent that:

* You are entitled to post the Comments on our website and have all necessary licenses and consents to do so;
* The Comments do not invade any intellectual property right, including without limitation copyright, patent or trademark of any third party;
* The Comments do not contain any defamatory, libelous, offensive, indecent or otherwise unlawful material which is an invasion of privacy
* The Comments will not be used to solicit or promote business or custom or present commercial activities or unlawful activity.

You hereby grant JeFawk Games a non-exclusive license to use, reproduce, edit and authorize others to use, reproduce and edit any of your Comments in any and all forms, formats or media.

### **Hyperlinking to our Content**

The following organizations may link to our Website without prior written approval:

* Government agencies;
* Search engines;
* News organizations;
* Online directory distributors may link to our Website in the same manner as they hyperlink to the Websites of other listed businesses; and
* System wide Accredited Businesses except soliciting non-profit organizations, charity shopping malls, and charity fundraising groups which may not hyperlink to our Web site.

These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Website information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products and/or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party’s site.

We may consider and approve other link requests from the following types of organizations:

* commonly-known consumer and/or business information sources;
* dot.com community sites;
* associations or other groups representing charities;
* online directory distributors;
* internet portals;
* accounting, law and consulting firms; and
* educational institutions and trade associations.

We will approve link requests from these organizations if we decide that: (a) the link would not make us look unfavorably to ourselves or to our accredited businesses; (b) the organization does not have any negative records with us; (c) the benefit to us from the visibility of the hyperlink compensates the absence of JeFawk Games; and (d) the link is in the context of general resource information.

These organizations may link to our home page so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party’s site.

If you are one of the organizations listed in paragraph 2 above and are interested in linking to our website, you must inform us by sending an e-mail to JeFawk Games. Please include your name, your organization name, contact information as well as the URL of your site, a list of any URLs from which you intend to link to our Website, and a list of the URLs on our site to which you would like to link. Wait 2-3 weeks for a response.

Approved organizations may hyperlink to our Website as follows:

* By use of our corporate name; or
* By use of the uniform resource locator being linked to; or
* By use of any other description of our Website being linked to that makes sense within the context and format of content on the linking party’s site.

No use of JeFawk Games's logo or other artwork will be allowed for linking absent a trademark license agreement.

### **iFrames**

Without prior approval and written permission, you may not create frames around our Webpages that alter in any way the visual presentation or appearance of our Website.

### **Content Liability**

We shall not be hold responsible for any content that appears on your Website. You agree to protect and defend us against all claims that is rising on your Website. No link(s) should appear on any Website that may be interpreted as libelous, obscene or criminal, or which infringes, otherwise violates, or advocates the infringement or other violation of, any third party rights.

### **Your Privacy**

Please read Privacy Policy below.

### **Reservation of Rights**

We reserve the right to request that you remove all links or any particular link to our Website. You approve to immediately remove all links to our Website upon request. We also reserve the right to amen these terms and conditions and it’s linking policy at any time. By continuously linking to our Website, you agree to be bound to and follow these linking terms and conditions.

### **Removal of links from our website**

If you find any link on our Website that is offensive for any reason, you are free to contact and inform us any moment. We will consider requests to remove links but we are not obligated to or so or to respond to you directly.

We do not ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we promise to ensure that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up to date.

### **Disclaimer**

To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions relating to our website and the use of this website. Nothing in this disclaimer will:

* limit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury;
* limit or exclude our or your liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation;
* limit any of our or your liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or
* exclude any of our or your liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law.

The limitations and prohibitions of liability set in this Section and elsewhere in this disclaimer: (a) are subject to the preceding paragraph; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under the disclaimer, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort and for breach of statutory duty.

As long as the website and the information and services on the website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature.

Privacy Policy & GDPR
=====================

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.  

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering, registering, surfing or using apps and games on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address, a nickname or other details to help you with your experience. Your IP address might also be recorded as anonimously as possible for tracking reasons and sometimes by our third party partners for targeted advertising. We collect any information we receive from you regarding selling products, and shipping them (such as name, address, phone number, etc). We do not hold on to this information more than needed for us to sell and ship the product to you. We do not sell any information.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site or when you utilize apps or games or provide us with feedback on our products or services.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  

      **•** To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

      **•** To improve our website in order to better serve you.

      **•** To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

      **•** To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

      **•** To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products

      **•** To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**

      **•** Keep track of advertisements.

      **•** Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you turn cookies off it will turn off some of the features of the site.

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.  
  
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en  

We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.

**GDPR**

We offer the option to agree or disagree with providing consent related to GDPR in every game on the website.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf  

**According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:**  

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.  

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

      **•** On our Privacy Policy Page  

Can change your personal information:

      **•** By emailing us

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**  

We don't honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. We don't honor them because:  

we cannot be sure that all our advertising partners honor them.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**  

It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.  

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.  

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify you via email

      **•** Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.  

**We collect your email address in order to:**

      **•** Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

      **•** Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**

      **•** Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

      **•** Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

      **•** Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

      **•** Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

      **•** Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

      **•** Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**

      **•** Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

**Disclaimer about the Ad technology providers**

We may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our website. Depending on the ads that are served, your data may be shared with any of the ad technology provider listed below. Ad technology providers (including Google, Ad Exchanges, SSPs, DSPs, ad networks, bidders and vendors) use your data for example, to show you personalised ads or to report on conversions. In the overview below you can find links to information on how the technology providers use your data.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Ad technology providers | Further info on how the ad technology providers use your data |
| Google | [https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/) |
| Aarki | [http://corp.aarki.com/privacy](http://corp.aarki.com/privacy) |
| Adacado | [https://www.adacado.com/privacy-policy-april-25-2018/](http://www.adacado.com/privacy-policy-april-25-2018/) |
| Adara Media | https://adara.com/2018/04/10/adara-gdpr-faq/ |
| AdClear | [https://www.adclear.de/datenschutzerklaerung/](http://www.adclear.de/datenschutzerklaerung/) |
| ADEX | [http://theadex.com](http://theadex.com/) |
| Adform | https://site.adform.com/uncategorized/product-and-services-privacy-policy/ |
| Adikteev | [https://www.adikteev.com/eu/privacy/](http://www.adikteev.com/eu/privacy/) |
| AdLedge | https://adledge.com/data-privacy/ |
| Adloox | [http://adloox.com/disclaimer](http://adloox.com/disclaimer) |
| Adludio | https://adludio.com/termsandconditions |
| AdMaxim | [http://www.admaxim.com/admaxim-privacy-policy/](http://www.admaxim.com/admaxim-privacy-policy/) |
| Admedo | [https://www.admedo.com/privacy-policy](http://www.admedo.com/privacy-policy) |
| Admetrics | https://admetrics.io/en/privacy\_policy/ |
| Adobe Advertising Cloud | [https://www.adobe.com/privacy/general-data-protection-regulation.html](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/general-data-protection-regulation.html) |
| AdRoll, Inc. | [https://www.adroll.com/gdpr](http://www.adroll.com/gdpr) |
| AdTriba | https://privacy.adtriba.com/ |
| advanced STORE GmbH | [https://www.ad4mat.com/en/privacy/](http://www.ad4mat.com/en/privacy/) |
| Adventori | [https://www.adventori.com/fr/avec-nous/mentions-legales/](http://www.adventori.com/fr/avec-nous/mentions-legales/) |
| advolution.control | [http://advolution.de/privacy.php](http://advolution.de/privacy.php) |
| affilinet | [https://www.affili.net/uk/footeritem/privacy-policy](http://www.affili.net/uk/footeritem/privacy-policy) |
| Akamai | [http://www.akamai.com/compliance/privacy](http://www.akamai.com/compliance/privacy) |
| Amazon | [https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010](http://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010) |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Amobee | [https://www.amobee.com/trust/privacy-guidelines](http://www.amobee.com/trust/privacy-guidelines) |
| Analights | https://analights.com/docs/analights-consent-to-the-processing-of-personal-data-en.pdf |
| AppLovin Corp. | [https://www.applovin.com/privacy](http://www.applovin.com/privacy) |
| AppNexus | [https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy](http://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy) |
| Arrivalist | [https://www.arrivalist.com/privacy#gdpr](http://www.arrivalist.com/privacy#gdpr) |
| AudienceProject | [http://privacy.audienceproject.com/for-users/](http://privacy.audienceproject.com/for-users/) |
| Aunica | [http://www.aunica.com/privacy/privacy.html](http://www.aunica.com/privacy/privacy.html) |
| Avocet | [http://avocet.io/privacy-portal](http://avocet.io/privacy-portal) |
| Batch Media | [http://batch.ba/datenschutzerklarung/](http://batch.ba/datenschutzerklarung/) |
| BDSK Handels GmbH & Co. KG | [https://www.xxxlutz.de/ocms/privacy](http://www.xxxlutz.de/ocms/privacy) |
| Beeswax | [https://www.beeswax.com/privacy.html](http://www.beeswax.com/privacy.html) |
| Betgenius | [http://betting.geniussports.com/connextra-service-terms-conditions/](http://betting.geniussports.com/connextra-service-terms-conditions/) |
| Bidswitch | [http://www.bidswitch.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.bidswitch.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Blismedia | [http://www.blis.com/privacy/](http://www.blis.com/privacy/) |
| Bombora | [http://bombora.com/privacy](http://bombora.com/privacy) |
| Booking.com | [https://www.booking.com/content/privacy.en-gb.html](http://www.booking.com/content/privacy.en-gb.html) |
| C3 Metrics | https://c3metrics.com/privacy |
| Cablato | [http://cablato.com/privacy](http://cablato.com/privacy) |
| Celtra | [https://www.celtra.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.celtra.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Centro | [https://www.centro.net/privacy-policy/](http://www.centro.net/privacy-policy/) |
| Cint | [https://www.cint.com/participant-privacy-notice/](http://www.cint.com/participant-privacy-notice/) |
| Clinch | https://clinch.co/pages/privacy.html |
| Cloud Technologies | [http://green.erne.co/assets/PolicyCT.pdf](http://green.erne.co/assets/PolicyCT.pdf) |
| Cloudflare | [https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/](http://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/) |
| Commanders Act | [https://www.commandersact.com/en/privacy/](http://www.commandersact.com/en/privacy/) |
| comScore | [https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy](http://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy) |
| Conversant/CJ Affiliate | [https://www.conversantmedia.eu/legal/privacy-policy](http://www.conversantmedia.eu/legal/privacy-policy) |
| Crimtan | https://crimtan.com/privacy-ctl/ |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Criteo | [https://www.criteo.com/privacy/](http://www.criteo.com/privacy/) |
| CUBED | [http://cubed.ai/privacy-policy/gdpr/](http://cubed.ai/privacy-policy/gdpr/) |
| DataXu | [https://www.dataxu.com/gdpr/](http://www.dataxu.com/gdpr/) |
| Delta Projects | [http://www.deltaprojects.com/data-collection-policy/](http://www.deltaprojects.com/data-collection-policy/) |
| Demandbase | [https://www.demandbase.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.demandbase.com/privacy-policy/) |
| DENTSU | [http://www.dentsu.co.jp/terms/data\_policy.html](http://www.dentsu.co.jp/terms/data_policy.html) |
| Dentsu Aegis Network | [http://www.dentsu.com/termsofuse/data\_policy.html](http://www.dentsu.com/termsofuse/data_policy.html) |
| Digiseg | [http://www.digiseg.io/GDPR/](http://www.digiseg.io/GDPR/) |
| DMA Institute | [https://www.dma-institute.com/privacy-compliancy/](http://www.dma-institute.com/privacy-compliancy/) |
| DoubleVerify | [https://www.doubleverify.com/privacy/](http://www.doubleverify.com/privacy/) |
| Dstillery | https://dstillery.com/privacy-policy/ |
| DTS | https://client.adhslx.com/privacy.html |
| EASYmedia | [https://www.rvty.net/gdpr](http://www.rvty.net/gdpr) |
| eBay | [https](http://www.ebay.com/help/policies/member-behaviour-policies/user-privacy-notice-privacy-)://www.ebay.com/help/policies/member-behaviour-policies/user-privacy-notice-privacy- policy?id=4260#section12 |
| ebuilders | [http://ebuilders.nl/privacy](http://ebuilders.nl/privacy) |
| Effinity | [https://www.effiliation.com/politique-confidentialite.html](http://www.effiliation.com/politique-confidentialite.html) |
| emetriq | [https://www.emetriq.com/datenschutz/](http://www.emetriq.com/datenschutz/) |
| Ensighten | [https://www.ensighten.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.ensighten.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Essens | https://essens.no/privacy-policy/ |
| ESV | [https://www.wizaly.com/terms-of-use#privacy-policy](http://www.wizaly.com/terms-of-use#privacy-policy) |
| Evidon | [https://www.evidon.com/resources/privacy-statement/](http://www.evidon.com/resources/privacy-statement/) |
| Exactag | [https://www.exactag.com/en/data-privacy/](http://www.exactag.com/en/data-privacy/) |
| Exponential | [http://exponential.com/privacy/](http://exponential.com/privacy/) |
| Facebook | [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update](http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update) |
| Flashtalking | [http://www.flashtalking.com/privacypolicy/](http://www.flashtalking.com/privacypolicy/) |
| Fractional Media | [https://www.fractionalmedia.com/privacy-policy](http://www.fractionalmedia.com/privacy-policy) |
| FUSIO BY S4M | [http://www.s4m.io/privacy-policy/](http://www.s4m.io/privacy-policy/) |
| Gemius | [https://www.gemius.com/cookie-policy.html](http://www.gemius.com/cookie-policy.html) |
| GfK | https://sensic.net/ |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| GP One | [http://www.gsi-one.org/templates/gsi/en/files/privacy\_policy.pdf](http://www.gsi-one.org/templates/gsi/en/files/privacy_policy.pdf) |
| gskinner | https://createjs.com/legal/privacy.html |
| Haensel AMS | https://haensel-ams.com/data-privacy/ |
| Havas Media France - DBi | [http://www.centraltag.com/commercial/policy/index.action](http://www.centraltag.com/commercial/policy/index.action) |
| hurra.com | [http://www.hurra.com/impressum](http://www.hurra.com/impressum) |
| IBM | [https://www.ibm.com/customer-engagement/digital-marketing/gdpr](http://www.ibm.com/customer-engagement/digital-marketing/gdpr) |
| Ignition One | [https://www.ignitionone.com/privacy-policy/gdpr-subject-access-requests/](http://www.ignitionone.com/privacy-policy/gdpr-subject-access-requests/) |
| Impact | https://impact.com/privacy-policy/ |
| Index Exchange | [http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/](http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/) |
| Infectious Media | https://impressiondesk.com/ |
| Innovid | [http://www.innovid.com/privacy-policy](http://www.innovid.com/privacy-policy) |
| Integral Ad Science | [http://www.integralads.com/privacy-policy](http://www.integralads.com/privacy-policy) |
| intelliAd | [https://www.intelliad.de/datenschutz](http://www.intelliad.de/datenschutz) |
| Interpublic Group | [https://www.interpublic.com/privacy-notice](http://www.interpublic.com/privacy-notice) |
| Jivox | [http://www.jivox.com/privacy/](http://www.jivox.com/privacy/) |
| Kantar | [https://www.kantarmedia.com/global/privacy-statement](http://www.kantarmedia.com/global/privacy-statement) |
| Kochava | [https://www.kochava.com/support-privacy/](http://www.kochava.com/support-privacy/) |
| LifeStreet | [http://www.lifestreet.com/privacy](http://www.lifestreet.com/privacy) |
| Liftoff | https://liftoff.io/privacy-policy/ |
| LiveRamp | https://liveramp.com/service-privacy-policy/ |
| Localsensor | [https://www.localsensor.com/privacy.html](http://www.localsensor.com/privacy.html) |
| LoopMe | https://loopme.com/privacy/ |
| Lotame | [https://www.lotame.com/about-lotame/privacy/](http://www.lotame.com/about-lotame/privacy/) |
| Macromill group | [https://www.metrixlab.com/privacy-statement/](http://www.metrixlab.com/privacy-statement/) |
| MainADV | [http://www.mainad.com/privacy-policy](http://www.mainad.com/privacy-policy) |
| Manage.com | [https://www.manage.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.manage.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Marketing Science Consulting Group, Inc. | [http://mktsci.com/privacy\_policy.htm](http://mktsci.com/privacy_policy.htm) |
| MBR Targeting Gmbh | https://privacy.mbr-targeting.com |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| MediaMath | [http://www.mediamath.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.mediamath.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Meetrics | [https://www.meetrics.com/en/data-privacy/](http://www.meetrics.com/en/data-privacy/) |
| MindTake Research | [https://www.mindtake.com/en/reppublika-privacy-policy](http://www.mindtake.com/en/reppublika-privacy-policy) |
| Mobitrans | [http://www.mobitrans.net/privacy-policy/](http://www.mobitrans.net/privacy-policy/) |
| Mobpro | [http://mobpro.com/privacy.html](http://mobpro.com/privacy.html) |
| Moloco Ads | [http://www.molocoads.com/private-policy.html](http://www.molocoads.com/private-policy.html) |
| MSI-ACI | [http://site.msi-aci.com/Home/FlexTrackPrivacy](http://site.msi-aci.com/Home/FlexTrackPrivacy) |
| Nano Interactive | [http://www.nanointeractive.com/privacy](http://www.nanointeractive.com/privacy) |
| Navegg | [https://www.navegg.com/en/privacy-policy/](http://www.navegg.com/en/privacy-policy/) |
| Neodata Group | [https://www.neodatagroup.com/en/security-policy](http://www.neodatagroup.com/en/security-policy) |
| NEORY GmbH | [https://www.neory.com/privacy.html](http://www.neory.com/privacy.html) |
| Netflix | [http://www.netflix.com/google-3PAS-info](http://www.netflix.com/google-3PAS-info) |
| Netquest | [https://www.nicequest.com/us/privacy](http://www.nicequest.com/us/privacy) |
| Neuralone | https://web.neural.one/privacy-policy/ |
| Neustar | [https://www.home.neustar/privacy](http://www.home.neustar/privacy) |
| Nielsen | [http://www.nielsen.com/us/en/privacy-statement/digital-measurement.html](http://www.nielsen.com/us/en/privacy-statement/digital-measurement.html) |
| Nordic Factory Solutions AB | [https://www.bannerflow.com/privacy](http://www.bannerflow.com/privacy) |
| numberly | [http://ads.1000mercis.com/us.html](http://ads.1000mercis.com/us.html) |
| Oath | https://policies.oath.com/xw/en/oath/privacy/enterprise/b2bprivacypolicy/ |
| Objective Partners | [https://www.objectivepartners.com/cookie-policy-and-privacy-statement/](http://www.objectivepartners.com/cookie-policy-and-privacy-statement/) |
| Omnicom Media Group | [https://www.omnicommediagroup.com/disclaimer.htm](http://www.omnicommediagroup.com/disclaimer.htm) |
| On Device Research | https://ondeviceresearch.com/GDPR |
| OneTag | [https://www.onetag.net/privacy/](http://www.onetag.net/privacy/) |
| OpenX Technologies | [https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/](http://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/) |
| Optomaton | [http://optomaton.com/privacy.html](http://optomaton.com/privacy.html) |
| Oracle Data Cloud | [https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/marketing-cloud-data-cloud-privacy-policy.html](http://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/marketing-cloud-data-cloud-privacy-policy.html) |
| OTTO | [https](http://www.otto.de/shoppages/service/about/datenschutzinformation/aboutprivacyneedtokno)://www.otto.de/shoppages/service/about/datenschutzinformation/aboutprivacyneedtokno w |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| PERMODO | [http://permodo.com/de/privacy.html](http://permodo.com/de/privacy.html) |
| Pixalate | [http://www.pixalate.com/privacypolicy/](http://www.pixalate.com/privacypolicy/) |
| Platform161 | https://platform161.com/cookie-and-privacy-policy/ |
| PMG | [https://www.pmg.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.pmg.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Protected Media | [http://www.protected.media/privacy-policy/](http://www.protected.media/privacy-policy/) |
| Publicis Groupe | [https://www.publicismedia.de/datenschutz/](http://www.publicismedia.de/datenschutz/) |
| PubMatic | https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy-policy/ |
| PulsePoint | [https://www.pulsepoint.com/privacy-policy](http://www.pulsepoint.com/privacy-policy) |
| Quantcast | [https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/](http://www.quantcast.com/privacy/) |
| Rackspace | [http://www.rackspace.com/gdpr](http://www.rackspace.com/gdpr) |
| Rakuten Marketing | https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy |
| Refined Labs | [https://www.refinedlabs.com/datenschutz-rfa](http://www.refinedlabs.com/datenschutz-rfa) |
| Relay42 | https://relay42.com/privacy |
| Remerge | [http://remerge.io/privacy-policy.html](http://remerge.io/privacy-policy.html) |
| Resonate | [https://www.resonate.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.resonate.com/privacy-policy/) |
| RevJet | [https://www.revjet.com/privacy](http://www.revjet.com/privacy) |
| RhythmOne LLC | [https://www.rhythmone.com/landing/gdpr](http://www.rhythmone.com/landing/gdpr) |
| RN SSI Group | [https://www.valuedopinions.co.uk/privacy](http://www.valuedopinions.co.uk/privacy) |
| Roq.ad | [https://www.roq.ad/privacy-policy](http://www.roq.ad/privacy-policy) |
| RTB House | [https://www.rtbhouse.com/gdpr/](http://www.rtbhouse.com/gdpr/) |
| Rubicon Project | [http://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-yield-optimization-privacy-policy/](http://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-yield-optimization-privacy-policy/) |
| Salesforce DMP | [https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/](http://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/) |
| Scenestealer | [http://www.scenestealer.tv/privacy-policy](http://www.scenestealer.tv/privacy-policy) |
| Scoota | [http://scoota.com/privacy-policy/](http://scoota.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Seenthis | https://seenthis.co/privacy-notice-2018-04-18.pdf |
| Semasio GmbH | [http://www.semasio.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.semasio.com/privacy-policy/) |
| SFR | [http://www.sfr.fr/securite-confidentialite.html](http://www.sfr.fr/securite-confidentialite.html) |
| Sift Media | [https://www.sift.co/privacy](http://www.sift.co/privacy) |
| Simpli.fi | [https://www.simpli.fi/site-privacy-policy2/](http://www.simpli.fi/site-privacy-policy2/) |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Sizmek | [https://www.sizmek.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.sizmek.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Smaato | [https://www.smaato.com/privacy/](http://www.smaato.com/privacy/) |
| Smadex | [http://smadex.com/end-user-privacy-policy/](http://smadex.com/end-user-privacy-policy/) |
| Smart | [http://smartadserver.com/company/privacy-policy/](http://smartadserver.com/company/privacy-policy/) |
| Smartology | [https://www.smartology.net/privacy-policy/](http://www.smartology.net/privacy-policy/) |
| Sociomantic | [https://www.sociomantic.com/privacy/en/](http://www.sociomantic.com/privacy/en/) |
| Sojern | [https://www.sojern.com/privacy/product-privacy-policy/](http://www.sojern.com/privacy/product-privacy-policy/) |
| Sovrn | [https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Spotad | [http://www.spotad.co/privacy-policy/](http://www.spotad.co/privacy-policy/) |
| SpotX | [https://www.spotx.tv/privacy-policy/](http://www.spotx.tv/privacy-policy/) |
| TabMo | [http://static.tabmo.io.s3.amazonaws.com/privacy-policy/index.html](http://static.tabmo.io.s3.amazonaws.com/privacy-policy/index.html) |
| Taboola | [https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy](http://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy) |
| TACTIC™ Real- Time Marketing | [http://tacticrealtime.com/privacy/](http://tacticrealtime.com/privacy/) |
| Teads.TV | https://teads.tv/privacy-policy/ |
| TEEMO | https://teemo.co/fr/confidentialite/ |
| The Trade Desk | [https://www.thetradedesk.com/general/privacy-policy](http://www.thetradedesk.com/general/privacy-policy) |
| Tradedoubler | [http://www.tradedoubler.com/en/privacy-policy/](http://www.tradedoubler.com/en/privacy-policy/) |
| travel audience – An Amadeus Company | https://travelaudience.com/product-privacy-policy/ |
| TreSensa | [http://tresensa.com/eu-privacy/index.html](http://tresensa.com/eu-privacy/index.html) |
| TripleLift | https://triplelift.com/privacy/ |
| TruEffect | https://trueffect.com/privacy-policy/ |
| TrustArc | [https://www.trustarc.com/privacy-policy/](http://www.trustarc.com/privacy-policy/) |
| Turbobytes | [https://www.turbobytes.com/gdpr/](http://www.turbobytes.com/gdpr/) |
| UDG | [https://www.udg.de/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/privacy\_policy\_EN.pdf](http://www.udg.de/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/privacy_policy_EN.pdf) |
| usemax (Emego GmbH) | [http://www.usemax.de/?l=privacy](http://www.usemax.de/?l=privacy) |
| Videology | https://videologygroup.com/en/privacy-policy/ |
| Vimeo | https://vimeo.com/cookie\_policy |
| Virtual Minds | https://virtualminds.de/datenschutz/ |

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Vodafone GmbH | [https://www.vodafone.de/unternehmen/datenschutz-privatsphaere.html](http://www.vodafone.de/unternehmen/datenschutz-privatsphaere.html) |
| Waystack | [https://www.wayfair.com/customerservice/general\_info.php#privacy](http://www.wayfair.com/customerservice/general_info.php#privacy) |
| Weborama | https://weborama.com/e-privacy/ |
| White Ops | [https://www.whiteops.com/privacy](http://www.whiteops.com/privacy) |
| Widespace | [https://www.widespace.com/legal/privacy-policy-notice/](http://www.widespace.com/legal/privacy-policy-notice/) |
| WPP | [https://www.groupm.com/mplatform-privacy-policy](http://www.groupm.com/mplatform-privacy-policy) |
| Yieldr | [https://www.yieldr.com/privacy/](http://www.yieldr.com/privacy/) |
| ZMS | https://zms.zalando.com/# |

Contact
-------

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us [here](https://jefawk.com/contact/index.html).

Last edited on 2024.Sep.11

### Some links 👀

### More links 😱

### Legal ⚖

### Talk to us here 💬🗨

Copyright © 2024 JeFawk & Frostnight Illustrations. All rights reserved.
